[
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "How many units are connected to the data bus:",
    "options": ["4 units", "5 units", "6 units"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "Addressing modes that doesn't exist in the calM:",
    "options": ["1- Based", "2- indexed indirect", "3- Based indexed"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "Instruction formats are:",
    "options": [
      "1- Reduced Format",
      "2- General Format ",
      "3- Neither of the two"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "How many bits are there in the flag register:",
    "options": ["1- 6 bits", "2- 7 bits", "3- 8 bits"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "How many bytes are there in the general purpose registers:",
    "options": ["1- One byte", "2- Two Bytes", "3- Three Bytes"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "What are the component that doesn't belong to the memory unit:",
    "options": ["1-IP", "2-CM", "3-MDR/MAR"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "All of the instructions are on 8 bits: ",
    "options": ["Yes", "No, all of them are on 16 bits ", "Neither of the two"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "How many bits are there in the flag register: ",
    "options": ["1- 6 bits", "2- 7 bits", "3- 8 bits"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "The cache memory is bigger than the central memory :",
    "options": [
      "1- Yes, it's bigger",
      "2- No, it's smaller",
      "3- They are equal"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "1",
    "question": "What are pointers in assembly?",
    "options": [
      "1- Variable type that stores integers",
      "2- Memory address that stores another memory address",
      "3- An I/O peripheral"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  }
]
